

Arman Ajabkhani

SENIOR JAVA DEVELOPER - BACKEND

PROFILE

Gender: Male

Nationality: Iranian Birth Date: 8/25/1983

I am a software engineer with more than 10 years'experience in software developing with Several roles including developer, designer, technical team lead in various projects.

Concentration, high interaction with team-mates, responsibility and perseverance, key observations in operational environments and issue solving are my main characteristics.

Learning new concepts, distributed systems and Software Quality(functional and non-functional) are interesting and exciting for me.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science from Sheikh Bahaee Isfahan University in Software Engineering from September 2000 to September 2006.

LANGUAGES

English

Persian

CONTACT

Email: arm.khani@gmail.com

Mobile: +98 912 8589 456

LinkedIn: Arman Ajabkhani's profile Address: No. 23, Parastoo2 Alley, Kaj St., Taherkhani St., Tehran, Iran

WORK EXPERIENCE

SNAPP(ride sharing)

Senior Java Developer

July 2019 - Present

My responsibility as a senior java developer.

- I developed reactive java using RxJava and Vert.x and Swagger.
- Responsible for designing and development of multiple services implementing Microservices.
- I design and implement feature in user account and notification implementing Microservices.

Sava Arman Kish(Crypto-currencies Exchange)

Senior Java Developer

Nov 2018 - Jul 2019

My responsibility as a senior java developer.

- I developed reactive java using RxJava and Vert.x and Swagger.
- Responsible for designing and development of multiple services implementing Microservices.
- I design and implement feature in user account and notification implementing Microservices.

TOSAN(Payment and Banking solution provider)

Senior Java Developer /Team Lead

Nov 2011 -Nov 2018

- Mentoring, coaching, training and planning tasks for the team members.
- Analysis, Design, Development, Deployment and Maintenance several applications and micro-services.
- Designing and developing some complicated features in open banking API.
- I worked as a member of the Channel Manger(CM) team.
- I developed functionalities for tracking and authentication and authorization.
- I developed and implemented Web Services with JAX-WS.
- I implemented many feature in Persistence layer using Hibernate
- I had Extensive experience using framework APIs like spring and Hibernate.

Elm o Sanat

Senior C#/ASP.NET Developer

Sep 2010 -Oct 2011

- I implement several new features in the School product.
- I used Entity Framework in school product and custom report generator.
- I implement virtual replication on SQL Server with use web service.

Netbina (Online Advertising)

Junior C#/ASP.NET Developer

October 2006 -March 2009



Arman Ajabkhani

SENIOR JAVA DEVELOPER - BACKEND

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

Core Java 8	Spring
SOA/Micro-services	Spring Boot
Test Driven Development	Spring MVC
Event Driven Architecture	Spring Batch
Software Architecture Patterns	Spring Security
Design Patterns	Spring Cloud
Live Migration	Spring Data / JPA/ Hibernate
Concurrent Programming	Spring AOP / aspectj
Reactive Programming	Vert.x / RxJava
RESTful Web Services	Redis / Redisson
SOAP / JAX-WS /JAX-RS	Oracle
Docker	MySQL / SQL Server
OpenShift	Gradle / Maven
Jenkins/Gitlab CI/CD	Swagger UI/ Codegen
Financial / Banking / Payment Systems	Git / Subversion / TFS
Crypto Currency Exchanges	ActiveMQ/ Rabbit MQ
UML/Agile and RUP Methodologies	Apache Tomcat
Confluence / SharePoint / Documenting	OAuth / JWT
Jira / TFS / HP ALM	JUnit / TestNg / Mockito
Scrum	<u>C</u> #
Distributed Systems	<u>MTEX</u>